http://www.wymans.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Last updated January 9, 2019
This Privacy Policy applies to Wyman’s digital platforms. This includes our websites, social media and mobile applications. This policy applies to all platforms where the policy is posted. This includes our company website at www.wymans.com.
This policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it, and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. If our information practices change, we will post an updated policy on our Site. You can tell if the policy has changed by checking the revision date that appears above. If we change the policy in a material way, we will provide notice to you and an opportunity to opt out of any new or different uses of your personal information. You may exercise your choices about how we collect and use your personal information consistent with this policy at any time.
WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT
Contact information. We collect information like your name or phone number. We may also collect your street address and email address.
Information you submit or post. We collect information you post in a public space on our websites.
Demographic information. We may collect information like your gender and age. We may collect your zip code (for example, to help you find a store that sells our products).
Other information. If you use our website, we may collect information about the browser you’re using. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us. In a mobile environment, we might collect your location.
Job application information. If you apply for a job, we collect information about you, your prior education and work history and your skills and qualifications for the position. We may ask about your salary expectations, how you learned of the position and your driving record or other information about your ability to perform the position. We may also collect the last four digits of your social security number and your nationality.
HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION
We collect information directly from you. We collect information if you sign up for a newsletter, enter a promotion or fill out an online survey. We also collect information if you make a purchase or apply for a job.
We collect information from you passively. We may use tracking tools like browser cookies and web beacons. We also collect information from our mobile apps.
We get information about you from third parties. For example, our business partners or social media platforms may give us information about you.
HOW WE USE INFORMATION
We use information to respond to your requests, questions, applications and entries. We may use your information to respond to your comments and questions, to notify you if you win a contest or sweepstakes or complete a purchase. If you apply for a job, we may use your information to process your application and determine if you are qualified.
We use information to improve our products and services. We may use your information to make our websites and products better. We might use your information to customize your experience with us. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.
We use information for security purposes. We may use information to protect our company, our customers, and our websites.
We use information for marketing purposes. For example, we might send you information about new products and special offers. We might tell you about new promotions, features or updates. These might be third party offers or products we think you might find interesting. We may also use push notifications on our mobile apps.
We use information to communicate with you about your account or our relationship. We may contact you about your account or feedback. We might also contact you about this Policy or our website Terms.
We use information as otherwise permitted by law.
SHARING INFORMATION
We may share information within Jasper Wyman and Son dba Wyman’s. This includes Wyman’s of Maine and Wyman’s.
We may share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf. For example, we share information with vendors so they can perform services for us. We may also share information with companies that operate our websites or run a promotion for us.
We may share information with joint promotion partners. Sometimes we conduct joint promotions with third parties. If you register for one of those joint promotions your information may be collected by both Wyman’s and the third party. Or, we may give you the option to have us share your information with the promotion partner. Your information will be used by us and/or by them as described in our posted privacy policies.
We will share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves. For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We might share information when we are investigating potential fraud. This might include fraud we think has happened during a sweepstakes or promotion.
We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you.
YOUR CHOICES ABOUT SHARING AND MARKETING PRACTICES
You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails. To stop receiving promotional emails from us, follow the instructions in any promotional message you get from us. Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will still send you transactional messages and respond to questions from you.
CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
If you reside in California, you have the right to ask us one time each year if we have shared personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make a request, please send us an email or write to us at the address listed below. Indicate in your letter that you are a California resident making a “shine the light” inquiry.
OUR SITES ARE NOT FOR KIDS
Our sites and apps are meant for adults and teens. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can contact us. Parents can learn more about how to protect children’s privacy on-line here: https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/topics/protecting-kids-online
WE USE STANDARD SECURITY MEASURES
The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords. We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.
WE STORE INFORMATION IN THE UNITED STATES
If you live outside of the U.S., you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States. This site is subject to U.S. laws, which may not afford the same level of protection as those in your country.
WE MAY LINK TO OTHER SITES OR HAVE THIRD PARTY SERVICES ON OUR SITE WE DON’T CONTROL.
If you click on a link to a third party site, you will be taken to websites or pages we do not control. This includes social media sites. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of third party websites. Read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for third party policies or practices.
Our site may also serve third party content that contains the third party’s own cookies or tracking technologies. We do not control the use of those technologies.
WE USE COMMON TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES
We collect personal information about users over time and across different Web sites when you use this Web site or service. We also have third parties that collect personal information this way. We use several common tracking tools to do this. Our vendors may also use these tools. These tools may include browser cookies or web beacons. We use these tools:
To recognize new or past customers.
To store your password if you are registered on our site.
To improve our website.
To serve you with advertising content in which we think you will be interested. To do so, we may observe your behaviors on this website and other websites. We may also collect information about your browsing history.
To better understand the interests of our customers and our website visitors.
YOU CAN CONTROL TRACKING TOOLS
Your browser may give you the ability to control cookies. How you do so depends on the type of cookie. Certain browsers can be set to reject browser cookies. If you block cookies on your browser, certain features on our sites may not work. Choices you make are both browser and device-specific. If you block or delete cookies, not all of the tracking that we have described in this policy will stop.
You can control tools on your mobile devices. For example, you can turn off the GPS locator or push notifications on your phone. Each push notification has an “unsubscribe” link. Some browsers have a “Do Not Track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. These features are not yet uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to those signals.
OUR ADS MAY BE SERVED BASED ON TRACKING
We may work with online advertising companies to show you relevant and useful ads. This includes ads served on other companies’ sites. These ads may be served based on information collected by us or third parties. For example, information a third party collects when you register for a site, like your zip code. This might be used to target an ad for people in your area. These ads may also be based on your activities on our websites or on third party sites.
YOU CAN OPT-OUT OF ONLINE BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING
To opt out of having your online behavior collected for advertising purposes, visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices. Choices you make are both browser and device-specific.
CONTACT US IF YOU HAVE MORE QUESTIONS
If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact Wyman’s Consumer Relations:
By Phone: (207) 541-0899
Online: Contact Us Form
WE MAY UPDATE THIS POLICY.
From time to time we may change our privacy policies. We will notify you of any material changes to our Policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our website. Please check our site periodically for updates.
© 2019 Wyman’s
